OK, so the first thing we'll do is create a new folder on the main.
And call it Web page.
OK.
And Hugh will include our Web page files, so have the Web page files handy that were provided from
the resources for this section so that we can include them in this folder.
And I have mine right here, so I'll just take all of these files and then copy them to the web page
folder like so.
And here, just choose copy files.
OK.
So now let's open the files that we're going to develop further throughout the course.
First, go to APT, get success and right click and go to open with.
And then choose other.
And I'll just choose the C C++ editor, but if you happen to have something better like VSCO, then
by all means please use that instead.
OK.
And then now let's choose the judges file and bring up the internal editors again.
And again, I'll choose C C++ editor.
And then open up the index study HTML document in the same manner.
And I'll choose the same editor.
And this is the template that will expand upon throughout the course.
Here we have our app, that CSIS file specified as the stylesheet, an app that JS file here and we
have a J query here as our JavaScript library.
And if we go over to D.J.s.
We already have the functions there, which will handle the firmware update on the web page side.
So feel free to look at this and get a basic understanding of it, and we'll add quite a bit of code
to it later.
Also, there is a very basic stylesheet here, and there's some button styling already here, as well
as some color and fonts as well.
You could always customize this so that it suits your needs.
All right, so let's head over to see make list file.
And here we're going to say embed files.
Because we need to embed the Web page files.
So we'll say the path web page slash app, that success.
And then Web page slash apt, James.
And Web page slash favicon, Iko.
And then Web page.
Index that HTML and then Lesli Web page slash.
And then let's copy the J query.
And pasted here and then we can save it.
OK, so now let's head over to the main folder and then a new source file.
And call it HTP server does see.
All right.
And now create a new -- file.
And call it HTP Server Dot H.
OK, so first, let's head it back over to see make lists and add the HTP server source file.
And save it.
So now let's go to tasks common.
And here we're going to define the HTP server task info.
So now let's define the HTP server.
Task stack size.
As eight thousand one hundred ninety two bites.
And then to find the.
HTTP server task priority.
And we'll define it is for.
Which is just one priority level under the Wi-Fi application desk.
Right in here, we can define the HGTV server task.
Core aid.
And we'll make it zero as well.
So now here we can define the HGTV server, monitor task info.
And first will define the.
HGTV server monitor.
Stack size.
As four thousand ninety six bytes.
And then for the HTP server monitor.
Priority.
We'll say three.
And then let's do the.
HGTV server monitor carried.
And this we can leave at zero.
OK, so let's takes care of our task info.
So now let's go over to the head of file and he will create messages for the HTP monitor.
And let's typedef enum.
HTP server message.
And the first one will be 8TB Message, wi fi connect and it.
And will explicitly set it to zero.
OK, and then the 8TB message, wi fi connect success.
And then we'll also have a message why if I connect, fail.
And then also HTP message OTA update successful.
And then HTP message OTA update failed.
And also HTP message OTA update initialized.
All right.
So let's name it as HGTV server message.
Underscore E for Enum, and so these are the messages that the HTP server monitor will handle for now.
The monitor really doesn't do anything complex.
I just had the idea to include it to react to events and update global variables within the monitor
only so that it's easier to track what's going on in the HTP server, as you'll see later, and you
can easily modify this as you wish.
OK, so now let's create a structure for the message queue.
And here will say typedef struck.
And tag it as a server Q message.
And here we'll just include the inner.
And call it message I.D..
Then let's call this HTP server Q message underscore T.
And don't forget the semicolon here.
And similar to the wife by ABC's messages, this is something that you can easily expand upon based
on your needs.
OK, so now let's come down here and create a prototype for a function that sends a message to the cube.
And so the first parameter is message ID.
From the HTP server message in.
And the return is true.
If an item was successfully sent to the queue.
Otherwise, PD false.
And I'll leave a note here for you to expand the parameter list based on your requirements.
E.g., how you've expanded the HTP server cube message structure.
OK, so just expand the struct and function, however you like.
Now, let's say base type underscored T.
HTTP server monitor.
Send message.
And then let's just grab the inner.
And drop it here.
And we'll create another prototype that starts the HTTP server.
And say void HGTV servers start.
And it's void.
All right, so now create another prototype that stops the HGTV server.
And it's void HGTV server stop.
And void.
So now that's it for now.
And in the next section, we'll call the HP server debt see file.